[{"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R3.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L2.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg", "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R4.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["下"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填", "stem": "填一填。", "animalImg": ["v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg", "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蝴蝶_F1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R6.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "str", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "面。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input8", "keyboardtype": "txt"}], "answers": ["上"], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-06"}]